Guide to the George and Louise Spindler Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Papers
  - Anthro. 1, 1973 February 5-October 10 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Psychological Anthropology, 07/01/70 - 03/21/74 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Anthropology 190, 10/15/1973 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Anthro 255, 10/24/72-04/22/73 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Anth. 256, Educ. 315, 8/25/71-11/12/73 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Native Americans, 03/02/72-10/29/73 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Arvizu, Steve, 12/14/73-08/20/74 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Oleson, Ray, 11/23/1970 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Positions Open, 06/02/69-03/31/70 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Bredo, Eric (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Brim, John, 05/18/67-01/28/70 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Needham, Rodney, 11/5/68-3/16/70 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Fellowships Available, 10/25/1968 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Marks, 11/21/67-7/1/69 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Miller, George, 3/7/1973 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Morrissey, James, 5/22/69-5/23/69 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Sindell, Peter, 8/14/69-2/4/74 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Peggy Summer, 9/5/69-9/10/69 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Education and Anthropology AAA, 11/19/67-7/31/69 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Amer. Anthro. Assoc., 1/29/69-9/19/73 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - AAA - Membership for Antrho-Educ. People, 8/6/67-12/14/68 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - American Anthropologist, 1/3/66-11/13/72 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - American Anthropologist, Chron File - September 1964, 9/1/64-10/16/64 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Stanford - general, 11/7/68-8/20/69 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Michel Guite', 8/22/69-11/13/69 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Biography-G.S., 11/9/72-12/11/72 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Biography L. Spindler, 11/26/1973 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Professional-General, 2/13/69-4/26/74 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Permissions-publication, 10/6/69-5/5/73 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Grant Application, 11/3/66-2/1/74 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Professional Advice Requested of G.D.S., 5/5/71-4/11/74 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Studies in European Society, 5/29/73-1/23/74 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Ethos-journal, 5/28/71-10/30/72 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Educational Studies, 8/20/70-12/29/70 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - American Values Paper, Univ of Delawate 10/74, 3/14/74-5/6/75 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Questionare Material on Hallowell 11/74, 11/12/74-1/13/75 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Trips - Completed, 5/9/67-1/7/74 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Trip to Japan?, 5/8/1968 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Center for Central European Studies - Lohnes, 4/16/69-6/18/69 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - GS - Consulting Brameld-Cultural Foundations of Education, 12/31/68-3/12/69 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - AERA Research Training {roj. Feb 1-5 1969, 10/13/68-5/7/69 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Overseas Campuses, 7/30/68-2/5/73 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Stanford in Germany, 1/6/66-12/17/73 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Untitled (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - GS Consulting Fideler Community Studies, 11/19/68-12/5/69 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - GDS-European Correspondence, 11/26/1968 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - GDS Contributions to Published Books, 9/26/68-10/9/68 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Reviews- By Spindlers, 8/16/66-4/2/73 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Germany-Research, 1/3/68-8/6/74 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Consulting, 7/9/68-5/14/74 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Invitations Refused, 9/11/70-9/18/72 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - G-H-I, 5/12/65-5/24/67 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - [Research applications and proposals], 6/30/1967 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - GDS Reprints- Requests For, 8/13/68-4/6/73 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - NSF- Review of Projects, 3/27/69-7/31/69 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Indians-General, 12/14/66-11/07/72 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Menominee Indians, 7/13/66-5/26/74 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Blood Indians, 6/23/67-7/1/70 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Indians-Canadian, 1/25/67-8/23/68 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Alcatraz-Indians, 1/22/70-9/23/70 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Indian Education, 5/31/67-11/13/72 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - IA Inventory, negatives and originals, 9/19/68-12/12/72 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - John Singleton, 2/14/68-12/28/73 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Robert Textor, 12/15/66-7/14/72 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Wilson, Brian, 1/28/69-2/24/74 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Richard Warren, 8/6/67-9/22/71 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Wolcott, Harry, 12/20/71-8/13/74 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Personal-Miscellaneous, 5/26/67-7/14/75 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Sue and Lloyd, 7/5/67-8/26/74 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Wisconsin-General, 6/6/67-6/5/74 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Tyler Collection, 2/17/67-4/19/67 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Personal-Financial, 5/26/67-12/11/73 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - A, 10/26/65-3/24/66 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Mise B "c" D, 7/19/65-2/14/68 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Mise "F" E, 6/18/65-3/29/66 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Mise J-K-L, 9/23/65-1/3/68 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Mise "M", 7/19/65-4/19/67 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Mise "n"+"o", 8/20/65-12/13/66 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Mise "P" Q, 6/15/65-12/28/67 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Mise "R" S, 8/16/65-6/20/67 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Reviews, 9/15/65-12/1/65 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Social Sciences Study Com. (Gearing), 1/17/66-4/7/66 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Mise "w" "V", 7/27/65-6/25/67 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Y, 7/30/65-8/20/65 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Untitled, 7/15/64-8/16/66 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Untitled, 7/12/65-8/18/65 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Mise notes, info-Spindlers, 6/9/65-7/1/65 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - G.A.S-Personal, 4/17/64-11/11/65 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - G.A.S. Personal, 1/8/65-5/21/65 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Symposium on Personality Rice Univ. Houston-Nov., 4/15/66-11/15/66 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - [ditto masters] (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Will Not Be Published- Small Batches of Correspondence, 10/27/67-9/18/72 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Aceves, Joseph, 5/13/68-2/11/70 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Albert, Ethel, 3/25/64-2/4/67 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Bee, Robert, 12/6/1971 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Berndt, 1/14/65-2/15/68 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Bodine, 5/19/67-8/24/67 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Bonilla, Eduardo Seda, 3/23/65-12/22/70 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Buchler, Ira, 7/30/68-7/8/71 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Crumrine, N. Ross, 3/17/69-1/3/72 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - de Rios, Marlene, 2/3/70-4/28/71 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Edmonson, Munro, 8/10/71-7/19/72 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Elmendorf, Mary, 10/20/72-11/1/73 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Gibbs, James, 12/24/67-12/27/68 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Greenway, 11/22/71-4/25/72 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Gutkind, Peter C. W., 3/28/67-4/6/73 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Heider, Karl, 12/1/66-12/11/69 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Hohepa, 6/21/67-9/25/67 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Jocano, 9/11/70-5/29/72 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Lewis, Herbert, 8/21/72-12/13/72 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Lundsgarrde, 10/25/66-5/9/68 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Martin, M. Kay, 11/7/72-1/16/74 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Maybury-Lewis, David, 9/18/61-6/6/72 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Montgomery, Evelyn, 12/8/66-9/5/67 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Sarana, 6/30/66-4/27/67 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Stamps (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - HRW Accounts, 3/27/73-8/15/73 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Holt Rinehart Winston Correspondence-I975, 1/8/75-8/4/75 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Holt Rinehart Winston Correspondence- 1974, 1/3/74-12/23/74 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Holt Rinehart Winston Correspondence- 69-73, 1/17/69-12/17/73 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Holt Rinehart Winston Correspondence- 1964, 1/29/64-12/23/64 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Holt Rinehart Winston Correspondence- 1965, 1/13/65-12/21/65 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Holt Rinehart Winston Correspondence- 1962, 1/4/62-12/19/62 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Holt Rinehart Winston Correspondence- 66-68, 1/4/65-11/18/68/1/19/59-11/17/61 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Holt Rinehart Winston Correspondence- 1959-1961 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Holt Rinehart Winston Permissions, 7/9/69-5/1/75 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Untitled, 4/7/1972 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Office Machines, 1/2/63-9/8/75 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Payrolls- HRW, 8/4/66-2/26/75 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Petty Cash, 7/16/70-1/18/73 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Review Journals For HRW Publications, 3/7/68-8/5/73 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Case Studies- Reviews, 4/18/67-2/4/70 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Holt Rinehart Winston Sales, 2/2/70-4/19/74 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Advertizing, 9/20/71-10/14/71 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Pricing- Case Studies (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Untitled, 7/5/66-11/8/73 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Case Studies in Education and Culture- General, 4/10/67-2/4/74 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Case Studies in Cultural Anthropology- General, 7/9/69-5/5/70 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Prospective Series in Archaeology, 11/2/67-3/26/73 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Case Studies- Audiovisual, 1/3/70-2/20/73 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Untitled (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Advisory Editorship- General July- December 1966, 8/4/1966 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Advisory Editorship- General January- June 1966, 1/17/66-4/20/66 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Critiques- Texts, 6/1/1968 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Advisory Editorship- General 1965, 2/23/65-10/5/65 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Advisory Editorship Prospects, 8/5/65-9/7/72 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Abler, Thomas, 5/4/70-7/7/70 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Barnett, C. - Med. Auth Text, 6/21/1971 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Alland, Alex, 8/22/1968 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Armelagos, George, 9/26/1968 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Bailey, Wilfrid, 12/9/66-6/19/70 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - [Bailey & Clune Manuscript of RACE] (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Bateson, Gregory, 8/21/1970 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Beals, Alan- Reader- Culture in Process, 12/2/68-2/5/69 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Bicchieri, Marco, 11/10/67-4/13/71 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Boissevain, Jeremy, 3/26/68-2/23/71 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Bock, Philip K. (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Brain, James, 5/26/69-7/8/69 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Burger, Henry, 10/25/68-3/16/74 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Burling, Robbins, 3/7/68-9/16/69 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Chance, Norman, 12/24/68-5/7/70 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Chapple, Eliot, 9/15/67-3/4/69 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Colby, Benjamin, 11/5/68-3/5/69 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Coult, Allan, 11/6/68-7/10/69 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Darnell, Regna (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Deetz, James- Series of Site Report, 12/1/66-6/28/67 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Downs, James, 5/13/70-11/15/72 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Downs, James F., 1/7/66-11/11/66 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Dozier, Edward, 9/15/67-10/27/67 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Dunn, Stephen P., 7/13/1970 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Edmonson, Munro, 1/6/69-8/11/69 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Fernandez, James W., 6/5/65-10/4/68 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Freeman, Derek, 3/19/71-8/26/71 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Freilich, Morris (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Ganst, Frederick C., 12/2/68-3/26/74 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Glick, Leonard, 11/3/71-4/10/72 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Goldschmidt, Wally, 9/16/68-10/7/68 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Graves, Theodore, 10/7/69-10/17/69 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Gumpers, John, 8/9/68-6/5/70 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Hamilton, James, 5/31/67-9/22/70 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Hostetler, 2/17/70-4/23/70 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Kay, Paul, 9/15/65-4/26/66 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Keesing, Roger, 9/17/71-3/26/76 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Keesing, 10/30/73-11/14/73 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Keiser, Lincoln, 9/18/70-10/9/70 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Keiser, Lincoln, 10/27/70-12/11/70 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Kopytoff, 2/6/65-8/17/65 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Kottack, 12/10/1969 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - LeClair, 5/19/65-7/9/69 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - LeClair (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Maloney, Clarence, 10/8/70-1/26/73 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Mann, Charles, 4/17/1968 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Mickey, Barbara, 4/1/1971 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Miller, Frank C., 4/4/66-5/13/69 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Moore, Sally Falk, 6/18/66-8/11/67 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Nader, Laura, 4/9/1969 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Nelson, Harold (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Olien, Michael, 6/17/70-8/12/72 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Oswalt, Wendell, 8/26/68-10/30/73 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Park, George, 11/1/65-12/17/69 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Partridge, William, 3/2/74-4/19/74 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Pearson, Roger, 6/2/71-10/16/73 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Riviere, Peter, 9/22/1971 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Rogers, Everett, 4/7/67-11/15/67 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Sackett, James, 2/28/67-4/25/67 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Schusky, 1/8/74-5/20/74 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Schusky- Cultural Anth. Text, 5/6/65-11/7/72 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Schwartz, Theodore, 5/21/69-3/17/70 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Service, Elman, 12/12/67-9/18/70 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Spindler, Guide to Cultural Anthro., 10/10/1968 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Spoehr, Alexander, 3/31/66-12/6/67 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Stocking, George, 12/21/65-2/7/66 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Taylor, Carol, 1/15/69-9/29/70 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - Thomas, David, 10/26/71-7/17/74 (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - Tyler, Stephen A., 3/29/65-9/17/69 (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - Waterbury, 11/27/1968 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - White, Douglas, 10/23/68-2/11/70 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Willems, Emilio, 7/8/69-12/2/69 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Williams, Thomas Rhys- Method Text, 11/26/68-4/16/74 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Williams, Thomas Rhys- Human Culture Transmitted, 2/3/68-12/3/69 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Worth, Sol, 6/21/67-7/11/67 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Untitled, 8/7/79-6/27/80 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Culture In Process- General, 12/16/66-10/17/73 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Schonhausen (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - [Researching The Psychology of Culture Change] (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Louise's Witchcraft Paper- 1968, 2/2/1967 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Education+Cultural Process- Permissions, 6/13/73-5/3/75 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Spindler, Louise (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Untitled (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Benn, G., 4/6/52-4/15/52 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Untitled, 2/23/1955 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Untitled, 4/21/56-10/18/63 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Forms etc. San Jose cases (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Case 69.9A Spring '52, 5/8/52-6/11/52 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Untitled, 11/1/50-11/24/58 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Record, 8/10/55-7/20/56 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Bibliography from Other (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Case 69.8a Sprg, 1952, 4/25/52-5/8/52 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Case 69.91a Spring-'52, 4/28/52-5/8/52 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Horace Mann Schl., 5/15/1952 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Trace Elementary, 3/10/1952 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Untitled, 11/1/1950 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Rorschach- all grouping, 11/20/50-3/13/51 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - [Bibliography], 11/13/1947 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Positions listed, Anth, Soc, 10/1/1958 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Mailing List, 10/22/1958 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence- 1957-, 11/19/57-9/30/58 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Urban Studies (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Thirtha, 9/4/1957 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Jampolsky, 4/27/56-5/1/56 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Dissertation Abstracts (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Doc. Exams/ Education, 3/17/54-11/26/57 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Honor Code- Other Univ. Blurbs, 3/28/55-3/30/56 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence- 1955, 1/28/55-6/3/56 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Accreditation, 4/28/1954 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - CRISS, 10/18/54-10/29/54 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - CRISS, 10/18/54-10/29/55 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Memos, etc.- Education, 8/4/55-11/25/57 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Untitled, 8/2/1954 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - 1st Conf. Ed&Anth 12/27/52, 12/27/1950 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Anth. Conf., 12/6/50-12/27/50 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Bartley Project (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - 1951 Stanford Salaries (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Course Recommendations and Joint Appt., 8/3/1951 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Case Outline Mimeograph (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Whitcomb- Personal, 6/19/1953 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Kellog Case Outline, 10/23/51-12/13/51 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Education, 7/17/52-4/13/53 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Public Documents + Book Lists (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, 3/20/52-12/10/58 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Untitled, 6/23/1950 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Consultation Service- Blurbs, 12/6/50-3/13/51 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Forms Recommended, 2/27/51-3/13/51 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Prof. Rorschachs Stat's, 4/20/51-12/8/52 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - PHD Research Plans Sharpe, Shipnuck, Christiansen, Tilden, 10/6/49-2/7/52 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Social Class (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Extra Bibliographies (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - TIAA, CREF, Soc Security, 12/8/50-5/27/54 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Public Health Service Exam Ques, 1/20/1954 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Teacher Ed., 11/30/195 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Humphreys, 8/12/51-12/3/51 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Ed Psych (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - End of Course Rating Forms (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Family Service, 11/2/1951 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Angier, 5/18/1955 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Angier, P.H. (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Dept. of Soc&Anthro, 12/7/49-6/5/55 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Educational Psychology 115, Summer Session 1951 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Intergroup Relations, 1/19/50-3/20/51 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Ed 115 Questionaires and Proj Material Summer '51, 6/25/1951 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Class evaluation of TAT Summer- '51, 7/16/1951 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Ed 115 Projective Materials Fall ' 51, 9/29/51-10/9/51 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Untitled, 6/11/1949 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Research on Prejudice- 46-47 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Anthro 3- Sep'47 end of course (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Soc 1 mid-course (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Quic Section Notes (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - [Contemporary American Values As Interpreted by Anthropologists] (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Cultural Process in Stable & Dynamic Situations (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Untitled (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Projects for 6L China Section March 1944 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Willow Glen- Grouping, 10/24/50-4/30/51 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Jefferson- Grouping, 11/20/50-5/18/51 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - General- MTG Reports- etc., 11/9/50-5/21/51 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - James Campbell, 11/15/50-8/15/51 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Selma Olinder- Grouping, 4/21/50-4/3/51 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Alemeda Conrad, 2/1/1951 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Recommendations Forms submitted- etc., 10/12/50-10/19/50 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Untitled (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Form 28, 28.1, 28 .11, 28.12- 69.3A, 1/15/51-5/4/51 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - 69.3A, 3/15/51-4/10/51 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Thut 69.3A Edison, 12/13/50-3/1/51 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - 69.1t Summary Materials, 1/11/51-6/8/51 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - 69.1t- graphs (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Magill 69.1 T Edison, 1/11/51-5/10/51 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - 69.1t FS.2 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - 69.1t F2, Pratys of Students (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - 69.1 t, 3/3/1951 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - 69.1t, 1/23/51-3/6/51 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - 69.lt Status Rep. (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Untitled (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - 69.lt 1.1+1.2, 1/14/51-3/29/51 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - 69.lt Edison/Sociogram Social Status, 2/8/1951 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - 69.2t- graphs Case Summary Materials, 1/8/51-6/7/51 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Current File 69.2t, 2/5/51-5/11/51 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - 69.2t Old Class Milliron Edison, 1/13/51-1/30/51 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - 69.2t F2 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - 69.2t F8.2, 1/23/51-1/31/51 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - 69.4t Special Materials For Bush, 1/17/51-5/3/51 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - 69.4t Summary Folder, 1/18/51-6/8/51 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - 69.4t- graphs (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Oppenheimer- Porter 69.4t, 2/1/51-4/3/51 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Purposes 69.4t, 3/29/51-4/10/51 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - 69.4t F3: 1, 1/22/1951 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - 69.4t Oppenheimer, 2/7/1951 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - 69.4t F2 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - 69.4t Sociograms- pricing, 4/11/51-4/18/51 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - 69.4t F1 Ratings of Students, Undated (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Sociogram Material 69.4t, Undated (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Summary 79.1t, 1951 January 23-April 25 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - 79.1t Thieman San Jose, Undated (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - 79.1t, 1951 January 23-May 8 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - 79.1t Interviews, Undated (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - 79.1t Tats and Ror, 1951 February 8-February 27 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - 79.1t F23-24, Undated (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - 79.1t Guess Who, Undated (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - 79.1t, F2, Undated (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Thimann, 79.1t, Undated (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Proj Materials: Ed Psych 115, 1952 Winter (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Ed Project-TAT Evaluation, 1952 Winter (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Ed 115 TAT+Husni, 1951 November 13-19 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - End of Course Evaluation Ed. 115, 1951 December 5 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Class Evaluations of James taken before projective materials, Undated (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Seminar 219, Undated (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Overhead slides, Undated (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Personal Data./c/S.J. 79.3A, 1952 October 27-1953 June 4 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Graphs/C.S.J. 79.3A, Undated (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - g/Personal+Inter Material 79.4A, 1952 November 18-1953? January 20 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - 79.4A F28 adm 28.1 Tchr, 1952 December 1-2 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Graphs/g./79.4A SJ, 1953 June 4 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Staff R 79.4A Sections 183 Russ+Shipwick's Forms, Undated (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - F15-79.4A/Info abt Tchrs, 1953 February 23 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - 79.4A 1.2 Adm. Rating of Tchr, 1953 April 19 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Staff Relations Sec I Part II Sect. III 79.3A, Undated (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - 79.3A/CF1.2 Adm. Rtg of Tchrs, 1953 April 2-4 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - 79.3A F28-28.1-28.11 28.12, 1952 December 8-1953 April 1 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Untitled, 1957 December 20-1958 January 22 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Untitled, Undated (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Untitled, Undated (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Untitled, Undated (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Untitled, Undated (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - 79.1t F14, 1951 May 8 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Untitled, 1954 May 5 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Form 32-What Do You Think of Your Supervisor?, 1951 July 6-9 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Rorschachs on Consult Service personal: To be completed, 1952 April 6-16 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Ed Psych 115, 1951 July 23-1952 January 25 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Ed Psych Text, Undated (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - ED 313. Socialization, Enculturation of the Child, Undated (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Base Map-Poplar Grove, 1951 April 6-13 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Anthropology 250, 1952 April 18-24 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Comparative Education, 1957 February 7 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - IBM Values Analysis, Undated (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Soc FND 110, Value Proj Test Autumn Quarter, 1954 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Value Proj. Test e110, 1955 Fall (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - e315 Value Test Ideal Boy, 1954-1955 Winter (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Values Projection Test S.Q. e110, 1955 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Open Ended Value Responses Social Fndtns, 1952 Fall (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Soc 110-Value Projections, 1953 Summer (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Ed 110-Value Projections Ideal Am. Boy, 1953 Fall (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Ideal Am. Boy. From 318 55,53, Undated (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Ed313-Ideal American Boy and Girl SP:54, 1954? (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Ideal American Bou Survey, Undated (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - 79.7A Stanford Consultation Service Staff Relations Survey Forms, Undated (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - 79.7A Stanford Consultation Service Survey Forms, Undated (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - 79.7A Stanford Consultation Service Survey Forms, Undated (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - 79.7A Stanford Consultation Service Survey Forms, Undated (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - A-F, 1970 October 2-1975 May 19 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - G-J, 1969 December 5-1975 May 28 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - K-M, 1970 January 7-1975 August 4 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - N-Z, 1970 July 7-1975 July 30 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - 221B G. and L. Spindler, Undated (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - ED 270H-G. and L. Spindler, Undated (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Bibliographic Selections ED270H, Undated (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Resrve Book List ED270H, 1991 Spring (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - ED270D-Reserve Book List, 1991 February 25 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Observation Record Guide Sheet, Undated (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - The Study of Cultural Transmission (Both Classes), Undated (Box 43, Folder 5)